A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, New Delhi, India, RG 6, SG 7 FA396
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Education, 1955-1973, n.d.; I5; 8 __Boxes __2.8 cubic feet
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Education - Institutional Files, 1957-1973, n.d.; I5.02
    - Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1959-1972 (Box 97, Folder 638)
    - Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1959-1972 (Box 97, Folder 639)
    - Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University - Land Shaping Operations, 1965-1971 (Box 97, Folder 640)
    - Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University - Maize Station, 1965-1973 (Box 97, Folder 641)
    - Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University - Staff Recruitment, 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 642)
    - Assam Agricultural University, 1961-1972 (Box 97, Folder 643)
    - Gujarat University, 1961, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 644)
    - Kerala Agricultural University, 1961-1962, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 645)
    - Madhya Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1961-1973 (Box 98, Folder 646)
    - Madhya Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1961-1973 (Box 98, Folder 647)
    - Madhya Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1961-1973 (Box 98, Folder 648)
    - Madhya Pradesh Agricultural University - Land Shaping Operations, 1965-1971 (Box 98, Folder 649)
    - Maharashtra Krishi Vidyapeeth College of Agriculture, 1965-1972 (Box 98, Folder 650)
    - Mysore University of Agricultural Sciences - Establishment, 1961-1966 (Box 98, Folder 651)
    - Mysore University of Agricultural Sciences - Establishment, 1961-1966 (Box 98, Folder 652)
    - Mysore University of Agricultural Sciences - Establishment, 1967-1973 (Box 99, Folder 653)
    - Mysore University of Agricultural Sciences - Staff Recruitment, 1964-1966 (Box 99, Folder 654)
    - Orissa University of Agriculture and Technology, 1960-1972 (Box 99, Folder 655)
    - Orissa University of Agriculture and Technology, 1960-1972 (Box 99, Folder 656)
    - Orissa University of Agriculture and Technology, 1960-1972 (Box 99, Folder 657)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, [1959]-1962, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 658)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, [1959]-1962, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 659)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, [1959]-1962, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 660)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, [1959]-1962, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 661)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 100, Folder 662)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 100, Folder 663)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 100, Folder 664)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 100, Folder 665)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Land Development, 1964-1965 (Box 100, Folder 666)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Staff Recruitment, 1965-1966, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 667)
    - Punjab Agricultural University - Staff Recruitment, 1965-1966, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 668)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Establishment, 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 669)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Establishment, 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 670)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 101, Folder 671)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 101, Folder 672)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Establishment, 1963-1973 (Box 101, Folder 673)
    - Rajasthan Agricultural University - Committee on Integration of Teaching, Research, and Extension, 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 674)
    - Tamil Nadu Agricultural University - Establishment, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 675)
    - Tamil Nadu Agricultural University/Agricultural College and Research Institute - Seed Production and Technology, 1966-1973 (Box 101, Folder 676)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1957-1963 (Box 101, Folder 677)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1957-1963 (Box 101, Folder 678)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1957-1963 (Box 101, Folder 679)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1964-1973 (Box 102, Folder 680)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1964-1973 (Box 102, Folder 681)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Establishment, 1964-1973 (Box 102, Folder 682)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Experiment Station Development, 1960-1965 (Box 102, Folder 683)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University - Experiment Station Development, 1960-1965 (Box 102, Folder 684)
    - West Bengal, Kalyani and Haringhata, 1959-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 685)
    - West Bengal, Kalyani and Haringhata, 1959-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 686)
- Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Research Institutes, 1956-1973; I6; 12 __Boxes __4.8 cubic feet
  Series 6, Agricultural Research Institutes, documents the RF's role in strengthening graduate agricultural education in India. The establishment of state agricultural universities, where Indian scientists could receive training, was deemed central to the success of the Indian Agricultural Program. A twin goal was the creation of a postgraduate school at the Indian Agricultural Research Institute (IARI), which occurred in 1958.
  Series 6, Agricultural Research Institutes, is arranged into three subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (IARI)
  Subseries 2 - Indian Institutions and Organizations
  Subseries 3 - International Research Institutes
  Within subseries, records are arranged alphabetically by subject, type of material, or name of institution.
  See also Subgroup I, Series 5 - Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Education.
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Research Institutes - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (IARI), 1957-1973; I6.01
    Subseries 1 (boxes 102-110) relates exclusively to the establishment and operation of the IARI Post Graduate School; it is divided into general correspondence and postgraduate school correspondence. General correspondence includes the office correspondence (1957-1973) of the IARI Director B. P. Pal; however, the bulk of the correspondence pertains to the IARI Department of Farm Operation and Management. This department provided farming service to the field work of all IARI divisions. These services included land preparation, irrigation, and machinery operation and maintenance. Among the correspondents are IARI directors B. P. Pal, A. B. Joshi, M. S. Swaminathan, and K. Kanungo, and Foundation Field Directors Ralph Cummings, Guy B. Baird, and Ordway Starnes.
    Postgraduate school correspondence (1956-1973) relates to the administration and organization of the school, in which IAP Field Director, Ralph W. Cummings played a leading role. He began discussions with IARI faculty and staff in January 1957 and served as the school's Acting Dean from 1959-1960. He was succeeded in 1960 by A. B. Joshi.
    Interfiled within the correspondence are minutes of faculty meetings and academic council meetings. Additional correspondence pertains to student eligibility for RF assistantships at IARI (1961-1973) and to academic divisions (1956-1973), especially Agricultural Engineering, Agricultural Physics, Farm Operations and Management, Genetics, and the Water Technology Centre.
    Records are arranged alphabetically by subject, type of material, or name of institution.
    - General Correspondence - Bird Control Operations, 1961-1967 (Box 102A, Folder 687)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1957-1961 (Box 102A, Folder 688)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1957-1961 (Box 102A, Folder 689)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1962-1973 (Box 103, Folder 690)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1962-1973 (Box 103, Folder 691)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1962-1973 (Box 103, Folder 692)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1962-1973 (Box 103, Folder 693)
    - General Correspondence - Director's Office Correspondence - Pal, B. P., 1962-1973 (Box 103, Folder 694)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Equipment - General, 1958-1971 (Box 103, Folder 695)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Equipment - MF 31-6 Combine, 1963-1967 (Box 103, Folder 696)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Equipment - Quarterly Reports of Equipment Supplied, 1957-1965 (Box 103, Folder 697)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Equipment - Quarterly Reports of Equipment Supplied, 1957-1965 (Box 103, Folder 698)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Equipment - Quarterly Reports of Equipment Supplied, 1966-1973 (Box 104, Folder 699)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Operations Development, 1957-1960, 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 700)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Operations Development, 1957-1960, 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 701)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Operations Development, 1957-1960, 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 702)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Operations Development, 1957-1960, 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 703)
    - General Correspondence - Farm Services Center, 1964-1966 (Box 104, Folder 704)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1958-1959 (Box 104, Folder 705)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1958-1959 (Box 104, Folder 706)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1960-1973 (Box 105, Folder 707)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1960-1973 (Box 105, Folder 708)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1960-1973 (Box 105, Folder 709)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1960-1973 (Box 105, Folder 710)
    - General Correspondence - Library, 1960-1973 (Box 105, Folder 711)
    - General Correspondence - Photo Laboratory, 1967-1971 (Box 105, Folder 712)
    - General Correspondence - Planning Unit, 1966-1968, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 713)
    - General Correspondence - Tile Drainage Project, 1959-1965, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 714)
    - General Correspondence - Tile Drainage Project, 1959-1965, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 715)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 716)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 717)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 718)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 719)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 720)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 721)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 722)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 723)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1970 (Box 106, Folder 724)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 107, Folder 725)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 107, Folder 726)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 107, Folder 727)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Dean's Office, 1970-1973 (Box 107, Folder 728)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Educational Testing, 1959-1961, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 729)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 730)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 731)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 732)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 733)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 734)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 735)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 736)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 737)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 738)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 739)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 740)
    - Post-Graduate School - Correspondence - Research Assistantships - Student Files (A-V), 1961-1973 (Box 108, Folder 741)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Chemicals, 1967-1973 (Box 108, Folder 742)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Economics, 1967-1970 (Box 109, Folder 743)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Engineering, 1959-1972 (Box 109, Folder 744)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Engineering, 1959-1972 (Box 109, Folder 745)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Extension Division, 1968-1971, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 746)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Physics, 1967-1973 (Box 109, Folder 747)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agricultural Physics, 1967-1973 (Box 109, Folder 748)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Agronomy, 1956-1973 (Box 109, Folder 749)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Biochemistry, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 750)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Entomology, 1969-1972 (Box 109, Folder 751)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Farm Operations and Management - General, 1967-1972 (Box 109, Folder 752)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Farm Operations and Management - General, 1967-1972 (Box 109, Folder 753)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Farm Operations and Management - Lists of Equipment Supplied, ca. 1970-1973 (Box 109, Folder 754)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Genetics - General, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 755)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Genetics - General, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 756)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Genetics - Cereal Quality Laboratory, 1966, 1971-1973 (Box 110, Folder 757)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Horticulture, 1968-1971, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 758)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Microbiology, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 759)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Microbiology, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 760)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Mycology and Plant Pathology, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 761)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Nuclear Research Laboratory, 1967-1968, 1971-1973 (Box 110, Folder 762)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Plant Physiology, 1971-1973 (Box 110, Folder 763)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Plant Introduction, 1967-1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 764)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Seed Technology, 1957-1959, 1965, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 765)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Water Technology Centre, 1966-1970, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 766)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Water Technology Centre, 1966-1970, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 767)
    - Post-Graduate School - Academic Divisions - Water Technology Centre, 1966-1970, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 768)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Research Institutes - Indian Institutions and Organizations, 1957-1973; I6.02
    In addition to the IARI in New Delhi, the RF assisted many Indian colleges, laboratories, and research institutes engaged in agronomic research and training. Subseries 2, Indian Institutions and Organizations, contains correspondence relating to RF support for such institutes, which generally included providing consultants, supplying and maintaining equipment, or recommending candidates to fill teaching positions. Files include RF evaluations of these institutes and their programs.
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute, 1957-1964, 1967-1970 (Box 111, Folder 769)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute, 1957-1964, 1967-1970 (Box 111, Folder 770)
    - Balwant Rajput College, Agra, 1961-1965 (Box 111, Folder 771)
    - Balwant Rajput College, Agra, 1961-1965 (Box 111, Folder 772)
    - Central Arid Zone Research Institute, Jodhpur, 1966-1969, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 773)
    - Central Tuber Crops Research Institute, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 774)
    - Date Palm Research Station, Abohar, 1959-1960 (Box 111, Folder 775)
    - Government Horticultural Research Institute, Saharanpur, 1957-1962 (Box 111, Folder 776)
    - Indian Council of Agricultural Research, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 777)
    - Indian Society of Soil Science, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 778)
    - Institute of Agriculture, Anand, 1957-1958, 1960-1962, 1964-1967 (Box 112, Folder 779)
    - Institute of Agricultural Research Statistics, New Delhi, 1959-1963, 1965-1966 (Box 112, Folder 780)
    - Institute of Horticultural Research, Bangalore, 1970-1972 (Box 112, Folder 781)
    - Institute of Pedology, 1961-1962 (Box 112, Folder 782)
    - National Dairy Research Institute, Karnal, 1970-1972 (Box 112, Folder 783)
    - Society for the Advancement of Breeding Researches in Asia and Oceana, 1970-1973 (Box 112, Folder 784)
    - Sri Avinashilingam Home Science College, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 785)
    - Vivekananda Laboratory, Almora, 1958-1960, 1962-1965, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 786)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Agricultural Research Institutes - International Research Institutes, 1955, 1958-1959, 1965-1973; I6.03
    Subseries 3, International Research Institutes, contains correspondence between the Delhi office and non-Indian research centers, including the Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) (1955-1973), Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) (1969-1973), and the International Uplands Crop Research Institute (1970-1973).
    - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT), 1955, 1958-1959, 1969-1972 (Box 112, Folder 787)
    - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) - Reports and Printed Material, 1966, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 788)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - General, 1969-1973 (Box 113, Folder 789)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - General, 1969-1973 (Box 113, Folder 790)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - Cooperation with All India Maize and Wheat Programs and Indian Council of Agricultural Research, 1971-1973 (Box 113, Folder 791)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - Maize and Germplasm Collection, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 792)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - Maize Planning Unit, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 793)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - Travel Arrangements for Visitors, 1971-1973 (Box 113, Folder 794)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1965-1966, 1968-1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 795)
    - International Uplands Crop Research Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 113, Folder 796)
    - International Uplands Crop Research Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 113, Folder 797)
    - International Uplands Crop Research Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 113, Folder 798)
    - International Uplands Crop Research Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 113, Folder 799)
- Indian Agricultural Program - Personnel Files, 1956-1973; I7; 24 __Boxes __9.6 cubic feet
  Subseries 1 - Regular Staff Members Subseries 2 - Temporary Staff Members Subseries 3 - Local Employees (Administrative and Service) Subseries 4 - Temporary Technical Employees Subseries 5 - Technical Employees, Rice Program
  Permanently restricted - Confidential material.
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Personnel Files - Regular Staff Members, 1958-1973; 7.01
    - Anderson, R. Glenn, 1963-1972 (Box 114, Folder 800)
    - Anderson, R. Glenn, 1963-1972 (Box 114, Folder 801)
    - Baird, Guy B., 1959-1971 (Box 114, Folder 802)
    - Baird, Guy B., 1959-1971 (Box 114, Folder 803)
    - Burress, C. G., 1963-1967, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 804)
    - Cummings, Ralph W., 1967-1972 (Box 114, Folder 805)
    - Cummings, Ralph W., 1967-1972 (Box 114, Folder 806)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1965-1973 (Box 114, Folder 807)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1965-1973 (Box 114, Folder 808)
    - Freeman, Wayne H., 1961-1975 (Box 115, Folder 809)
    - Freeman, Wayne H., 1961-1975 (Box 115, Folder 810)
    - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1964-1972 (Box 115, Folder 811)
    - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1964-1972 (Box 115, Folder 812)
    - Hopper, W. David, 1966-1970 (Box 115, Folder 813)
    - Hopper, W. David, 1966-1970 (Box 115, Folder 814)
    - House, Leland R., 1959-1972 (Box 115, Folder 815)
    - House, Leland R., 1959-1972 (Box 115, Folder 816)
    - Pomeroy, C. R., 1965-1972 (Box 116, Folder 817)
    - Pomeroy, C. R., 1965-1972 (Box 116, Folder 818)
    - Quick, James S., 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 819)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1957-1968 (Box 116, Folder 820)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1957-1968 (Box 116, Folder 821)
    - Randall, Frederick F., 1964-1969 (Box 116, Folder 822)
    - Renfro, B. L., 1960-1972 (Box 116, Folder 823)
    - Renfro, B. L., 1960-1972 (Box 116, Folder 824)
    - Sprague, Ernest W., 1958-1967 (Box 116, Folder 825)
    - Wright, William C., 1963-1970 (Box 116, Folder 826)
    - Young, William R., 1961-1973 (Box 117, Folder 827)
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Personnel Files - Temporary Staff Members, 1957-1972; 7.02
    - Armstrong, Ray E., 1961-1963 (Box 117, Folder 828)
    - Bonn, George S., 1968-1971 (Box 117, Folder 829)
    - Bonn, George S., 1968-1971 (Box 117, Folder 830)
    - Bonn, George S., 1968-1971 (Box 117, Folder 831)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1963-1971 (Box 117, Folder 832)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1963-1971 (Box 117, Folder 833)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1973 (Box 118, Folder 834)
    - Bradfield, Richard, 1958-1964 (Box 118, Folder 835)
    - Burton, Glenn W., 1962-1963 (Box 118, Folder 836)
    - Carter, A. S., 1967 (Box 118, Folder 837)
    - Chapman, Homer D., 1960-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 838)
    - Chapman, Homer D., 1960-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 839)
    - Chapman, Homer D., 1960-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 840)
    - Erion, Gerhardt W., 1962-1967 (Box 118, Folder 841)
    - Fireman, Milton, 1960-1965 (Box 118, Folder 842)
    - Hagan, Robert M., 1960-1967 (Box 119, Folder 843)
    - Hagan, Robert M., 1960-1967 (Box 119, Folder 844)
    - Harrington, James F., 1968-1970 (Box 119, Folder 845)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1957-1959, 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 846)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1957-1959, 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 847)
    - Herdt, Robert W., 1966-1968, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 848)
    - Hodgson, Robert W., 1958-1966 (Box 119, Folder 849)
    - Hodgson, Robert W., 1958-1966 (Box 119, Folder 850)
    - Holton, C. S., 1966-1967 (Box 119, Folder 851)
    - Horsfall, James G., 1961-1962 (Box 119, Folder 852)
    - Hrabovszky, J. P., 1962-1963, 1965, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 0852a)
    - Johnson, A. A., 1960-1962 (Box 119, Folder 853)
    - Johnston, J. E., 1971 (Box 120, Folder 854)